Take a quick look and if there are no questions on any of those four items and entertain a motion to approve the staff's recommendation
For the consent agenda. There's no further discussion. Make folks do approve and a second
roll call please
I had a nine as a new business and a new business
Ten as staff reports written reports in your packet for available staff as president if you have questions. I think
11 is
Marin Council announcements any announcements anyone
I then 12 is same as if your communication is deemed you have anything for us
Is on the 19
And that's also when the chamber count, but it is I believe a lot of us are going to be doing
I know we have at least two items on the agenda, but I don't anticipate it's going to be a packed agenda
But we come to order at 530 here and then trying to get out of the book will run for the
Gallo, probably is going to cut it off or close
So I was going to suggest that possibly we cancel our meeting on the 19
knowing that the following week following on the 26th will have our study session scheduled and we can have some of our
As well as any items that we would talk about at the study session that of course starts at 430s at 530
So I just wanted to see if that would create any difficulty for me if you or
That way we can probably accommodate both both items
Well, I can't go into the gal
I don't have a problem with a tentatively planning that leave it on the schedule until we get closer
Okay, something comes up right and then
If there's something really pressing the short we could even start a little bit early if we needed to it was called a special meeting for that after
And you know at 5 or something
But if
Lester's any objections will tanively
Plan that's not have that meeting and make sure that we're here for the following week for the work session
We can't let you out. Okay, okay, okay, okay. Okay, excuse me
I'm 13 this meeting is going to be continued from council chambers
In reconvening the meeting room one for purposes of the executive session
I'm going to we need to make the motion before we leave or can we do that in the meeting room
It was make the motion to
Reconvening in that room
Immediately, okay, then I will call in there
And I will say what I need to say for you at that point.
And then the adjournment will be from that beginning.
Also, maybe we're in one.
OK.
So do we actually need to make a motion to adjourn and reconvene
or we just get up and go?
Well, as the agenda to do that, that I always make this cleaner.
If we do make the motion and you all vote to do that.
OK.
So do we have a motion to adjourn this meeting briefly
and the reconvene in the meeting room?
Can you continue this meeting?
It continues.
Yes.
Thank you for that one.
I'll make it.
All right.
Roll, roll, please.
Who is I?
Good.
All right.
My stem.
Roll and start.
All right.